Guide to the AFL-CIO Region 9 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
AFL-CIO Region 9 records
1949-2000
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5189
5189-001
AFL-CIO.$bRegion No. 9
14.00 cubic feet 14 boxes
Records of this labor organization
After the 1955 merger of the American Federation of Labor and the Congress of Industrial Organizations, the national AFL-CIO implemented a regional system to communicate and coordinate with state and local labor councils. Since 1955, the regional system has been restructured several times. For the purposes of this collection, AFL-CIO Region 9 refers to the representative of the national AFL-CIO in the Pacific Northwest from 1986 to 1996. Located in Seattle, the office is now defunct, its former jurisdiction encompassed: Alaska, Idaho, Montana, Oregon and Washington. In 1996-1997, these areas were merged within new AFL-CIO regional office structure and placed under Western Region Office, in San Francisco, CA.
From 1986 until 1994, Region 9 was directed by Edward Collins. Previously, Collins had overseen the Region 6 office in San Francisco. David Gregory succeeded Collins in 1994. After the reorganization Gregory served as Regional Political Coordinator.
Due to the restructuring of the regional system this collection contains materials from AFL-CIO Region 21 (1955-1974) and AFL-CIO Region 6 (1974-1986). The AFL-CIO Region 21 office was located in Portland, Oregon and directed by Chester C. Dunsten (1956-1964), Claude Shaffer (1964-1965), and James J. Leary (1965-1974). The AFL-CIO Region 6 office was located in San Francisco and directed by William L. Gilbert (1974-1977), Charles Hogan (1977-1981), James Baker (1981-1983), and Edward J. Collins (1983-1986).
The collection is arranged into 14 series
Series I: AFL-CIO Alaska Records
Series II: AFL-CIO Idaho Records
Series III: AFL-CIO Montana Records
Series IV: AFL-CIO Oregon Records
Series V: AFL-CIO Washington Records
Series VI: AFL-CIO Arizona Records
Series VII: AFL-CIO California Records
Series VIII: AFL-CIO Colorado Records
Series IX: AFL-CIO Connecticut Records
Series X: AFL-CIO Indiana Records
Series XI: AFL-CIO Missouri Records
Series XII: AFL-CIO Nebraska Records
Series XIII: AFL-CIO Nevada Records
Series XIV: AFL-CIO Wyoming Records
Series I - V are AFL-CIO Region 9 materials divided by state. These series are then subdivided into two subseries by creator type: statewide labor council and local labor councils. The latter is further divided into sub-subseries by the creating body. Series VI - XIV are AFL-CIO materials from other Regions divided by state.
The collection consists of the records from the AFL-CIO Region 9 office. The collection includes records of local or state councils sent as information copies to the regional director. These records include: State Federation and Central Labor Council Constitutions and By-Laws, region director's correspondence, yearly reports, minutes, AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education (COPE), State and regional conferences and conventions, and Community Service Agencies. The collection contains subject files concerning various legislative issues, political candidates, organizing, collective bargaining, and boycotts.
Forms part of the Labor Archives of Washington.
Records stored offsite; advanced arrangements are necessary. Please contact us for more information.
No restrictions on access.
AFL-CIO
Collins, Edward; Gregory, David; AFL-CIO.$bRegion No. 9$vArchives; Oregon AFL-CIO; AFL-CIO.$bCommittee on Political Education; AFL-CIO$bCommunity Service Activities; AFL-CIO.$bOregon State Labor Council; AFL-CIO.$bWashington State Labor Council; Alaska State Federation of Labor; Idaho State Federation of Labor; Montana State AFL-CIO; Montana State Federation of Labor; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Alaska; Idaho; Montana; Oregon; Washington (State); Northwest, Pacific; Labor$zAlaska; Labor$zIdaho; Labor unions$zIdaho; Labor$zMontana; Labor$zOregon; Labor unions$zOregon; Labor$zWashington (State); Labor unions$zWashington (State)
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor Unions; Labor History
- AFL-CIO Alaska Materials, 1958-1995; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1-2/11)
  - Alaska State Federation of Labor Materials, 1974-1995; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/1-25)
    - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1982-1992 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Part 3: Executive Board Meetings, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 1/3-4)
      - Alaska AFL-CIO Executive Board, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Alaska State Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Part 4: Correspondence, 1982-1995 (Box-folder 1/5-15)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1990 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 1/12)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Alaska State Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Part 5: Conventions, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 1/16-19)
      - 1984 Alaska Convention - Fairbanks, Alaska, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 1/16)
      - 1991 Alaska State AFL-CIO Convention (Box-folder 1/17)
      - 1992 Biennial Convention - Alaska AFL-CIO (Box-folder 1/18)
      - Alaska Legislative Conference 1992 January 22-23 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Part 6: Committee on Political Education, 1974-1995 (Box-folder 1/20-21)
      - Alaska State Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1974-1984 (Box-folder 1/20)
      - Alaska State Legislative Reports, 1995 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Part 7: Community Services, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Part 8: Subject Files, 1978-1991 (Box-folder 1/23-25)
      - Alaska State Central and Local Bodies, 1978 (Box-folder 1/23)
      - Alaska State Charges, 1990 (Box-folder 1/24)
      - State of Alaska Health Care Cost Containment Task Force Report to the Seventeenth Legislature, 1991 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - Alaska Local Labor Councils, 1958-1993; Subseries B (Box-folder 1/26-2/11)
    - Anchorage Central Labor Council, 1981-1993; Sub-Subseries 1 (Box-folder 1/26-32)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 1/26-27)
        - Anchorage Central Labor Council Constitution and Bylaws, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 1/26)
        - Anchorage Central Labor Council Constitution and Bylaws, 1991 (Box-folder 1/27)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1980-1993 (Box-folder 1/28)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 1/29)
      - Part 4: Subject Files, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 1/30-32)
        - Anchorage Central Labor Council Local Community Services Profile, 1986 (Box-folder 1/30)
        - Anchorage Central Labor Council Bills/Anchorage, 1990 (Box-folder 1/31)
        - Anchorage Central Labor Council Valenzuela Charges, 1990 (Box-folder 1/32)
    - Fairbanks Central Labor Council, 1984-1991; Sub-Subseries 2 (Box-folder 1/33-36)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 1/33)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 1/34)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 1/35)
      - Part 4: Subject Files, 1989 (Box-folder 1/36)
        - Fairbanks Central Labor Council - Mailing Lists, 1989 (Box-folder 1/36)
    - Juneau Central Labor Council, 1961-1993; Sub-Subseries 3 (Box-folder 1/37-39)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1961-1985 (Box-folder 1/37)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1978-1993 (Box-folder 1/38)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 1/39)
    - Kenai Peninsula Central Labor Council, 1985-1993; Sub-Subseries 4 (Box-folder 2/1-3)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Ketchikan Central Labor Council, 1958-1991; Sub-Subseries 5 (Box-folder 2/4-7)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1958-1985 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1974-1991 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, Undated (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Sitka Central Labor Council, 1972-1990; Sub-Subseries 6 (Box-folder 2/8-11)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1972 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 2/11)
- AFL-CIO IDAHO MATERIALS, 1975-2000; SERIES II (Box-folder 2/12-4/46)
  - Idaho Federation of Labor, 1979-2000; Subseries A (Box-folder 2/12-4/6)
    - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1985-1994 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1985-1993 (Box-folder 2/13-16)
      - Idaho State Yearly Reports, 1985-1993 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Idaho State Monthly Financial Reports, 1991 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Idaho State Monthly Financial Reports, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Idaho State Officers Election Reports, 1986 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Part 3: Excutive Board Meetings, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 2/17-25)
      - Idaho State Board Meeting 1987 October 13 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Idaho State Finance Committee, Executive Board, 1988 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Idaho State Board Meeting Agenda, 1989 October (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Idaho State Executive Board Meetings, 1990 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Idaho State Executive Board Meeting, 1990 February (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Idaho State Executive Board Meeting, 1990 April (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Idaho State Executive Board Meeting, 1990 June (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Idaho State Executive Board Meeting 1992 February 29 (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Idaho State Executive Board Meeting 1992 June 6 (Box-folder 2/25)
    - Part 4: Correspondence, 1982-2000 (Box-folder 2/26-3/6)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 2/27)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 2/28)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2/29)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 2/30)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 2/31)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 2/32)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Idaho State Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Idaho State Correspondence Files, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Part 5: Conventions, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 3/7-9)
      - Idaho State December 1981 Workshops (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Idaho State Convention, 1990 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Idaho State Convention 1992 June 8-10 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Part 6: Committee on Political Education, 1981-1993 (Box-folder 3/10-16)
      - Idaho State Committee on Political Education, 1992 (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Idaho State Committee on Political Education Convention, 1990 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Idaho State Legislation and Elections, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Idaho State 1984 Election (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Idaho State 2nd Congressional District Legislative Action Committee, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Idaho State Idaho Elections, 1990 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Idaho State 1st Congressional District Legislative Action Committee, 1993 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Part 7: Community Services, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 3/17-19)
      - Idaho State Community Service Agencies, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Idaho State United Way, 1990 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Idaho State American Red Cross, 1990 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Part 8: Subject Files, 1979-1996 (Box-folder 3/20-4/6)
      - Idaho State Affiliation Reports, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Idaho State Central and Local Bodies, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Idaho State 1980-1983 Chronological Files, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Idaho State Central Labor Councils Handbook and Materials, 1989 (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Idaho State Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Idaho State Northern Idaho Lists, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 3/25)
      - Idaho State John Evans, 1982 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Idaho State Sunshine Reports, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Idaho State Black List Workers Compensation, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Idaho State Southern Idaho Master Labor Agreement, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Idaho State Building Trades Council Panel, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Idaho State Loan Information, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Idaho Local Labor Councils, 1975-1995; Subseries B (Box-folder 4/7-46)
    - Boise Central Trades, 1981-1995 (Box-folder 4/7-17)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1983 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1985-1994 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1983 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Part 4: Executive Board Meetings, 1981-1993 (Box-folder 4/10-12)
        - Boise Central Trades - Executive Board Minutes, 1981-1993 (Box-folder 4/10)
        - Boise Central Trades - Minutes, 1986 (Box-folder 4/11)
        - Boise Central Trades - Minutes, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Part 5: Correspondence, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 4/13-14)
        - Boise Central Trades - Correspondence, 1986 (Box-folder 4/13)
        - Boise Central Trades - Correspondence, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Part 6: Committee on Political Education, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 4/15-16)
        - Boise Central Trades - Committee on Political Education, 1992 (Box-folder 4/15)
        - Boise Central Trades - Legislative Newsletters, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Part 7: Subject Files, 1983 (Box-folder 4/17)
        - Boise Central Trades - Idaho New Districts, 1983 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Canyon County Trades and Labor Council, 1977-1993; Sub-Subseries 2 (Box-folder 4/18-21)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1977 (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1983 (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1983-1993 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Cassia Doka Central Labor Council, 1983-1993; Sub-Subseries 3: (Box-folder 4/22-24)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 4/22)
      - Part 2: Correspondence, 1983-1993 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Part 3: Subject Files, 1990 (Box-folder 4/24)
        - Cassia Doka Central Labor Council - Cassia Doka and Twin Falls, 1990 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - East Idaho Central Labor Council, 1983-1995; Sub-Subseries 4 (Box-folder 4/25-27)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 4/25)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 4/26)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Lewiston Idaho Clarkston Washington Central Labor Council, 1984-1995; Sub-Subseries 5 (Box-folder 4/28-33)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1984-1993 (Box-folder 4/28-29)
        - Lewiston Idaho Clarkston Washington Central Labor Council - Yearly Reports, 1984-1993 (Box-folder 4/28)
        - Lewiston Idaho Clarkston Washington Central Labor Council - Books, 1992 (Box-folder 4/29)
      - Part 2: Executive Board Meetings, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 4/30-31)
        - Lewiston Idaho Clarkston Washington Central Labor Council - Minutes, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 4/30)
        - Lewiston Idaho Clarkston Washington Central Labor Council - 1990 July 17 Meeting (Box-folder 4/31)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 4/32)
      - Part 4: Subject Files, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 4/33)
        - Lewiston Idaho Clarkston Washington Central Labor Council - 990 Tax Info, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 4/33)
    - Northern Idaho Central Labor Council, 1987-1994; Sub-Subseries 6 (Box-folder 4/34-37)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 4/34)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 4/35)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 4/36)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 4/37)
    - Pocatello Central Labor Union, 1975-1992; Sub-Subseries 7 (Box-folder 4/38-41)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 4/38)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 4/39)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 4/40)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1983-1991 (Box-folder 4/41)
    - Twin Falls Central Labor Council, 1983-1992; Sub-Subseries 8: (Box-folder 4/42-43)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 4/42)
      - Part 2: Correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 4/43)
    - Shoshone County Trades and Labor Council, 1983-1988; Sub-Subseries 9 (Box-folder 4/44-46)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 4/44)
      - Part 2: Officers Election Reports, 1984 (Box-folder 4/45)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 4/46)
- AFL-CIO Montana Materials, 1963-1996; SERIES III (Box-folder 5/1-10/53)
  - Montana State Federation of Labor, 1963-1996; Subseries A (Box-folder 5/1-9/30)
    - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 5/2-4)
      - Montana State Yearly Reports and Financial Statements, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Montana State Financial Records, 1991 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Montana State Financial Reports, 1993 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Part 3: Executive Board Meetings, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 5/5-19)
      - Montana State Executive Board and Business Trust Meeting Minutes, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Montana State Executive Board Meeting 1990 April 28 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Montana State Executive Board Meeting 1990 April 28 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Montana State Executive Board Meeting 1990 August 15 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Montana State Executive Board Meeting 1990 November 10, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Montana State Executive Board Meeting 1991 August 21 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Montana State Executive Board Meeting 1991 January 5 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Montana State Executive Board Meeting 1991 August 3-4 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Montana State Executive Board Meeting 1993 June 23, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Montana State Executive Board Meeting 1993 June 23, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Montana State Executive Board Meeting 1992 June 24 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Montana State Business Trust Meeting 1992 June 24 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - Montana State Business Trust 1991 May 4 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Montana State Trust Meeting 1991 August 21 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - Montana State Business Trust Meeting 1994 January 8, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Part 4: Correspondence, 1982-1996 (Box-folder 5/20-7/1)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1982-1983 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1986 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1989 1 of 6 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1989 2 of 6 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1989 3 of 6 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1989 4 of 6 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1989 5 of 6 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1989 6 of 6 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Montana State Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Montana State Correspondence, 1990 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1992 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1992 (Box-folder 6/10)
      - Montana State Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Montana State Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - Montana State Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Montana State Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 6/14)
      - Montana State Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Montana State Correspondence 1995-1996 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Part 5: Conventions, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 7/2-14)
      - Montana State 32nd Annual Convention Yearbook Butte, 1988 August 18-20 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Montana State 33rd Annual Convention Yearbook Helena, 1989 August 17-19 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Montana State Central Labor Council Conference 1990 March 3-4 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Montana State Convention 1990 August 16-18 1 of 2, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Montana State Convention 1990 August 16-18 2 of 2, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Montana State Convention 1991 August 22-24 (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Montana State Building and Construction Trades Council Convention, 1991 (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Montana State Annual Convention 1992 June 25-27 1 of 2, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 7/9)
      - Montana State Annual Convention 1992 June 25-27 2 of 2, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Montana State Annual Convention Proceedings 1992 (Box-folder 7/11)
      - Montana State Building and Construction Trades Annual Convention 1992 June 23 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Montana State Annual Convention 1993 June 24-26 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Montana State Annual Convention 1993 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Part 6: Committee on Political Education, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 7/15-8/1)
      - Montana State Committee on Political Education, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Montana State Proposed Committee on Political Education Budget, 1990 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Montana State Committee on Political Education Workshop 1991 August 21, 1983-1991 (Box-folder 7/17)
      - Montana State 1988 Committee on Political Education Proposals, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 7/18)
      - Montana State Legislative Newsletter, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 7/19)
      - Montana State Elections, 1990 (Box-folder 7/20)
      - Report on the 1991 Montana State Legislature, 1991 June (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Montana State 1989 Legislative Report (Box-folder 7/22)
      - Montana State Election Committee, 1991 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Part 7: Community Services, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Part 8: Subject Files, 1963-1995 (Box-folder 8/3-9/30)
      - Montana State General File, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Montana State Communications, 1993 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Montana State Right to Work, 1979-1991 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Montana State Right to Work, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Montana State Right to Work Legislation, 1993 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Montana State Right to Work, 1995 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Montana State Budget Right to Work, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Montana State Timber and Wilderness Issue, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Montana State Wilderness Accords [Kootenai-Lolo] 1 of 2, 1990 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Montana State Wilderness Accords [Kootenai-Lolo] 2 of 2, 1990 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Montana State Family Union 1991 May 4, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Montana State Family Union Annual Meeting 1991 August 17 Helena, Montana (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Montana State Family Union, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Montana State Family Union Board of Directors Meeting 1991 August 17 Helena, Montana (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Montana State Family Union Membership Meeting 1992 May 16 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Montana State Family Union Articles of Incorporation, 1990 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Montana State Family Union Board of Directors Meeting 1994 January 8, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Montana State National Healthcare Campaign, 1986 (Box-folder 8/20)